[
    {
        "question": "In the first episode of squid game, what is Gi-Hun betting on?",
        "choice1": "College football",
        "choice2": "Horse racing",
        "choice3": "Basketball",
        "choice4": "Poker",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Gi-Hun's profession in squid game?",
        "choice1": "Accountant",
        "choice2": "Waiter",
        "choice3": "Chauffeur",
        "choice4": "Janitor",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people were contestants in the game?",
        "choice1": "656",
        "choice2": "566",
        "choice3": "486",
        "choice4": "456",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the shapes on the card given to the contestants?",
        "choice1": "Circle, Rectangle, Square",
        "choice2": "Circle, Triangle, Square",
        "choice3": "Triangle, Square, Star",
        "choice4": "Rectangle, Circle, Pentagon",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first game called?",
        "choice1": "Red Light, Green Light",
        "choice2": "Stop and Go",
        "choice3": "Freeze",
        "choice4": "Search and Destroy",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "What contestant number is Gi-Hun?",
        "choice1": "456",
        "choice2": "001",
        "choice3": "067",
        "choice4": "218",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "The police officer found out his brother competed in the game in what year?",
        "choice1": "2009",
        "choice2": "2013",
        "choice3": "2015",
        "choice4": "2018",
        "answer": 3
    },


    {
        "question": "What did Gi-Hun give to his daughter as a birthday gift accidentally?",
        "choice1": "A gun",
        "choice2": "A lighter",
        "choice3": "A doll",
        "choice4": "A stolen necklace",
        "answer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "Which shape on the guard's mask represented the highest rank?",
        "choice1": "Circle",
        "choice2": "Square",
        "choice3": "Triangle",
        "choice4": "Star",
        "answer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "What shape does Ali get in the second game?",
        "choice1": "Umbrella",
        "choice2": "Star",
        "choice3": "Circle",
        "choice4": "Triangle",
        "answer": 3
    } 
]